Paul	O
International	O
airport	O
atanga	O
lo	O
chhuak	O
a	O
ni	O
.	O

A	O
changtu	O
ber	O
chu	O
Hicks	B-person-artist/author
nupui	O
,	O
Ellaline	B-person-actor
Terriss	I-person-actor
leh	O
Edmund	B-person-actor
Payne	I-person-actor
te	O
an	O
ni.	O

``	O
Time	B-art-writtenart
``	O
magazine	O
chuan	O
he	O
film	O
hi	O
``	O
multimillion	O
dollar	O
improvisation	O
a	O
ni	O
a	O
a	O
title-in	O
a	O
tiam	O
tih	O
loh	O
chu	O
engkim	O
ti	O
thei	O
''	O
a	O
nih	O
thu	O
leh	O
``	O
writer	O
George	B-person-artist/author
Axelrod	I-person-artist/author
(	O
``	O
The	B-art-writtenart
Seven	I-art-writtenart
Year	I-art-writtenart
Itch	I-art-writtenart
``	O
)	O
leh	O
director	O
Richard	B-person-director
Quine	I-person-director
te	O
chuan	O
Holden	B-person-other
	O
's	O
character	O
Richard	B-person-other
Benson	I-person-other
	O
,	O
who	O
a	O
movie	O
a	O
ziak	O
a	O
a	O
thil	O
siam	O
chu	O
rei	O
tak	O
fimkhur	O
takin	O
a	O
en	O
a	O
a	O
hal	O
ta	O
a	O
ni	O
.	O
''	O

IAEA	B-organization-other
a	O
hnathawk	O
Pakistan	O
scientist	O
leh	O
engineer	O
te	O
chuan	O
India	O
nuclear	O
program	O
chu	O
bomb	O
siamna	O
lam	O
hawia	O
hmasawn	O
zel	O
an	O
nih	O
thu	O
an	O
hre	O
ta	O
a	O
ni	O
.	O

Kum	O
2008	O
February	O
thla	O
khan	O
Church	B-organization-company
's	I-organization-company
Chicken	I-organization-company
chu	O
UK	O
market-ah	O
``	O
Texas	B-organization-company
Chicken	I-organization-company
``	O
hmingin	O
a	O
lut	O
a	O
Dixy	B-organization-company
Chicken	I-organization-company
franchisee	O
hlui	O
50	O
zet	O
a	O
sign	O
up	O
thu	O
a	O
sawi.	O

Khawchhak	O
lama	O
sipai	O
leh	O
vengtu	O
awmte	O
pawh	O
hi	O
Assuria	O
mi	O
an	O
ni	O
.	O

Decorations	O
leh	O
chawimawina	O
hi	O
Croatian	B-location-GPE
emaw	O
ramdang	O
mi	O
legal	O
entity	O
bakah	O
Armed	O
Forces	O
of	O
the	B-location-GPE
Republic	I-location-GPE
of	I-location-GPE
Croatia	I-location-GPE
unit	O
leh	O
Ministry	O
of	O
the	O
Interior	O
te	O
hnenah	O
pek	O
theih	O
a	O
ni.	O

He	O
hripui	O
hian	O
Mediterranean	B-location-GPE
Basin	I-location-GPE
a	O
nghawng	O
nasa	O
ber	O
leh	O
a	O
nghawng	O
tam	O
ber	O
a	O
mahse	O
Near	B-location-GPE
East	I-location-GPE
leh	O
Northern	B-location-GPE
Europe	I-location-GPE
te	O
pawh	O
a	O
kai	O
ve	O
bawk.	O

Kum	O
2000	O
chho	O
tir	O
lam	O
atang	O
khan	O
inelna	O
hi	O
a	O
nasa	O
tan	O
hle	O
a	O
ni	O
.	O

Neville	B-person-athlete
chuan	O
Tozawa	B-person-athlete
chu	O
Spinning	O
Back	O
Kick	O
hmangin	O
title	O
a	O
humhim	O
.	O

A	O
awmna	O
hmun	O
atang	O
hian	O
Mrs.	B-person-other
Strong	I-person-other
chuan	O
Duke	O
of	O
Windsor	B-person-other
leh	O
Wallis	B-person-other
,	O
The	O
Duchess	O
of	O
Windsor	B-person-other
,	O
Barbara	B-person-other
Hutton	I-person-other
,	O
the	O
Rockefeller	B-person-other
,	O
Astor	B-person-other
,	O
Vanderbilt	B-person-other
,	O
leh	O
DuPont	B-person-other
te	I-person-other
tan	I-person-other
paper	I-person-other
a	I-person-other
siam	I-person-other
a	I-person-other
chhungkua	O
te	O
chubakah	O
Bette	B-person-other
Davis	I-person-other
,	O
Diana	B-person-other
Vreeland	I-person-other
,	O
Jacqueline	B-person-other
Bouvier	I-person-other
Kennedy	I-person-other
,	O
Barbara	B-person-other
Paley	I-person-other
,	O
leh	O
style	O
icon	O
dangte	O
pawh	O
an	O
tel.	O

As	O
a	O
result	O
of	O
outdoing	O
the	O
competition	O
,	O
Binion	B-person-other
chuan	O
thi	O
tura	O
vau	O
a	O
dawng	O
a	O
mahse	O
a	O
tawpah	O
chuan	O
casino-te	O
chuan	O
a	O
hnung	O
zui	O
zel	O
turin	O
an	O
limit	O
an	O
tisang	O
ta	O
a	O
ni.	O

A	O
hming	O
pawh	O
The	B-art-broadcastprogram
Gale	I-art-broadcastprogram
Storm	I-art-broadcastprogram
Show	I-art-broadcastprogram
:	I-art-broadcastprogram
Oh,	I-art-broadcastprogram
Susanna	I-art-broadcastprogram
tia	O
ngaih	O
a	O
ni	O
bawk.	O

Tualchhung	O
mite	O
chuan	O
``	O
Fairbottom	B-product-other
Bobs	I-product-other
``	O
tia	O
hriat	O
a	O
ni	O
a	O
tunah	O
chuan	O
Henry	B-building-other
Ford	I-building-other
Museum	I-building-other
-ah	O
Dearborn	B-location-GPE
,	O
Michigan	B-location-GPE
-ah	O
dah	O
a	O
ni.	O

Sheremetyevo	B-building-airport
International	I-building-airport
Airport	I-building-airport
hian	O
passenger	O
terminal	O
pali	O
leh	O
special	O
terminal	O
pakhat	O
chu	O
private	O
leh	O
business	O
aviation	O
hmanna	O
atana	O
dah	O
a	O
ni	O
.	O

He	O
hmunah	O
hian	O
Victoria	B-location-other
line	I-location-other
,	O
Northern	B-location-other
City	I-location-other
Line	I-location-other
,	O
leh	O
London	B-location-other
Overground	I-location-other
North	I-location-other
London	I-location-other
Line	O
te	O
chu	O
an	O
inzawm	O
khawm	O
a	O
ni	O
.	O

``	O
bite-and-hold	O
''	O
tactics	O
hmangin	O
thil	O
tum	O
chu	O
German	B-location-GPE
counter-attack	O
laka	O
neih	O
theih	O
tur	O
chauh	O
a	O
ni	O
a	O
British	B-location-GPE
te	O
chuan	O
German	B-location-GPE
defence	O
chu	O
an	O
tichhe	O
a	O
chu	O
chuan	O
German	B-location-GPE
commander	O
te	O
zingah	O
buaina	O
a	O
siam	O
a	O
4th	B-organization-other
Army	I-organization-other
te	O
rilru	O
a	O
hloh	O
nasa	O
hle	O
bawk.	O

Medical	O
school	O
kal	O
lai	O
khan	O
Reitman	B-person-other
hian	O
Boston	B-building-sportsfacility
Garden	I-building-sportsfacility
-a	O
infiamna	O
inelnaah	O
house	O
doctor	O
hna	O
a	O
thawk	O
fo	O
thin.	O

A	O
tlangpuiin	O
window	O
thar	O
a	O
lo	O
lan	O
chuan	O
a	O
hmaa	O
buffer	O
ang	O
chiah	O
kha	O
a	O
rawn	O
lang	O
thin	O
.	O

Tun	O
hma	O
chuan	O
Communiplex	B-building-other
tia	O
hriat	O
a	O
ni	O
a	O
WHL	B-organization-company
-a	O
Prince	O
Albert	B-person-other
Raiders	I-person-other
leh	O
Prince	O
Albert	B-person-other
Mintos	I-person-other
te	O
awmna	O
hmun	O
a	O
ni.	O

``	O
Spring	O
Breakdown	O
''-a	O
score	O
hi	O
Deborah	B-person-artist/author
Lurie	I-person-artist/author
siam	O
a	O
ni	O
a	O
ani	O
hian	O
Blake	B-person-artist/author
Neely	I-person-artist/author
kaihhruai	O
Hollywood	B-art-music
Studio	I-art-music
Symphony	I-art-music
hmangin	O
a	O
score	O
a	O
record	O
a	O
Greg	B-person-artist/author
Dennen	I-person-artist/author
chuan	O
Eastwood	B-event-other
Scoring	I-event-other
Stage	I-event-other
-ah	O
Warner	B-organization-company
Brothers	I-organization-company
-ah	O
a	O
record	O
bawk.	O

Damdawi	O
dawr	O
shelf-ah	O
brand	O
tam	O
tak	O
a	O
lang	O
a	O
formulation	O
hrang	O
hrangah	O
.	O

Swedish	B-organization-sportsteam
national	I-organization-sportsteam
mipa	I-organization-sportsteam
ice	I-organization-sportsteam
hockey	I-organization-sportsteam
team	I-organization-sportsteam
,	O
hmangaihna	O
nena	O
``	O
Tre	B-organization-sportsteam
Kronor	I-organization-sportsteam
``	O
(	O
English	B-other-language
:	O
Three	B-organization-sportsteam
Crowns	I-organization-sportsteam
;	O
Sweden	B-location-GPE
ram	O
chhinchhiahna	O
tia	O
hriat	O
chu	O
khawvela	O
team	O
tha	O
ber	O
pawla	O
ngaih	O
a	O
ni.	O

FBR-ah	O
hian	O
technical	O
leh	O
material	O
lama	O
harsatna	O
lian	O
tak	O
tak	O
a	O
awm	O
a	O
geological	O
exploration-ah	O
chuan	O
uranium	B-other-chemicalthing
tlakchhamna	O
chu	O
hun	O
engemaw	O
chen	O
chu	O
ngaihtuahawm	O
a	O
ni	O
dawn	O
lo	O
tih	O
a	O
lang	O

Palina	O
Audi	B-organization-sportsteam
leh	O
pangana	O
Jaguar	B-person-athlete
te	O
chu	O
point	O
khatin	O
an	O
inthlau	O
.	O

Memorial	B-building-hospital
Sloan-Kettering	I-building-hospital
Cancer	I-building-hospital
Center	I-building-hospital
Board	O
of	O
Overseers	O
member	O
a	O
ni	O
bawk.	O

United	B-other-law
States	I-other-law
Freedom	I-other-law
Support	I-other-law
Act	I-other-law
Section	O
907	O
chuan	O
Azerbaijani	B-location-GPE
sorkar	O
hnena	O
direct	O
United	B-location-GPE
States	I-location-GPE
tanpuina	O
chi	O
hrang	O
hrang	O
pek	O
khap	O
a	O
ni	O
.	O

He	O
hla	O
hi	O
Puerto	B-location-GPE
Rico	I-location-GPE
ah	O
Alpha	B-building-other
Recording	I-building-other
Studios	I-building-other
ah	O
record	O
a	O
ni.	O

Freighter	O
kalna	O
tur	O
hmun	O
hriat	O
duh	O
chuan	O
Air	O
China	O
Cargo	O
.	O

Downtown	O
Newark	B-location-GPE
leh	O
Elizabeth	B-location-GPE
te	O
chu	O
Newark	B-building-airport
Liberty	I-building-airport
International	I-building-airport
Airport	I-building-airport
hmanga	O
thlunzawm	O
tura	O
ruahman	O
a	O
ni	O
a	O
NJT	B-location-road/railway/highway/transit
chuan	O
Newark-Elizabeth	B-location-road/railway/highway/transit
Rail	I-location-road/railway/highway/transit
Link	I-location-road/railway/highway/transit
chu	O
a	O
zawm	O
tawh	O
lo.	O

Hoey	B-person-other
hi	O
Mallusk	B-location-GPE
,	O
County	B-location-GPE
Antrim	I-location-GPE
ah	O
a	O
piang	O
a	O
Belfast	B-organization-education
Royal	I-organization-education
Academy	I-organization-education
leh	I-organization-education
Ulster	I-organization-education
College	I-organization-education
of	I-organization-education
Physical	I-organization-education
Education	I-organization-education
ah	O
te	O
a	O
zir	O
a	O
ni.	O

Amazon	B-person-other
Prime	I-person-other
hla	O
``	O
Bosch	B-art-film
``	O
ah	O
Chief	O
Irvin	B-person-other
Irving	I-person-other
a	O
chang	O
a	O
ni.	O

Church	B-building-other
of	I-building-other
England	I-building-other
parish	I-building-other
kohhran	I-building-other
St	I-building-other
John	I-building-other
The	I-building-other
Evangelist	I-building-other
chu	O
Friern	B-location-road/railway/highway/transit
Barnet	I-location-road/railway/highway/transit
Road	I-location-road/railway/highway/transit
-ah	O
chuan	O
Grade	O
II	O
*	O
list-ah	O
a	O
awm	O
a	O
ni.	O

Samsat	B-location-island
district	I-location-island
thar	I-location-island
hi	O
peninsula	O
a	O
ni	O
a	O
a	O
sir	O
thum	O
atanga	O
Atatürk	B-location-bodiesofwater
Dam	I-location-bodiesofwater
Lake	I-location-bodiesofwater
in	O
a	O
hual	O
vel	O
a	O
ni.	O

Drill	B-building-other
hall	I-building-other
hi	O
a	O
sei	O
a	O
mansard	O
tower	O
sang	O
pahnih	O
a	O
nei	O
bawk	O
.	O

Nawrh	O
huaihawt	O
nan	O
tuna	O
Helikopter	O
Service	O
chuan	O
Braathens	B-organization-company
SAFE	I-organization-company
-in	O
Stavanger	B-location-GPE
atanga	O
a	O
kalpui	O
airline	O
route-te	O
chu	O
a	O
dil	O
a	O
mahse	O
he	O
dilna	O
hi	O
hnawl	O
a	O
ni	O

Bascule	O
bridge	O
hian	O
NJ	B-organization-other
Transit	I-organization-other
Rail	I-organization-other
Operations	I-organization-other
North	B-location-road/railway/highway/transit
Jersey	I-location-road/railway/highway/transit
Coast	I-location-road/railway/highway/transit
Line	I-location-road/railway/highway/transit
chu	O
Bradley	B-building-other
Beach	I-building-other
leh	O
Belmar	B-building-other
station	I-building-other
inkarah	O
a	O
phur	O
a	O
ni.	O

Raisna	B-location-GPE
Chauhan	I-location-GPE
hi	O
Uttar	B-location-GPE
Pradesh	I-location-GPE
state	O
,	O
India	B-location-GPE
-a	O
Meerut	B-location-GPE
district	I-location-GPE
-a	O
khaw	O
pakhat	O
a	O
ni	O
a	O
National	B-location-GPE
Capital	I-location-GPE
Region	I-location-GPE
(	I-location-GPE
NCR	I-location-GPE
)	I-location-GPE
-a	O
tel	O
a	O
ni.	O

Dan	O
chuan	O
corporativist	O
state	O
din	O
a	O
rawt	O
a	O
.	O

A	O
tihtlem	O
nasa	O
hle	O
laiin	O
Papal	B-location-GPE
States	I-location-GPE
chuan	O
chuti	O
chung	O
pawh	O
chuan	O
Latium	B-location-GPE
leh	O
Rome	B-location-GPE
chhim	O
thlang	O
lam	O
hmun	O
zau	O
tak	O
tak	O
chu	O
a	O
la	O
huam	O
vek	O
a	O
ni.	O

Package	O
pasarih	O
hi	O
tuna	O
operator	O
Widerøe	O
chuan	O
a	O
la	O
vek	O
a	O
ni	O
.	O

Hei	O
hi	O
Bicentennial	B-event-protest
Boycott	I-event-protest
movement	I-event-protest
zau	O
zawka	O
tel	O
a	O
ni	O
a	O
chu	O
chu	O
Bicentennial	B-location-GPE
hmaa	O
intan	O
a	O
ni.	O

Laccadives	B-location-island
te	O
hi	O
Maldives	B-location-island
te	O
nen	O
hian	O
an	O
insiam	O
dan	O
a	O
danglam	O
a	O
ni.	O

The	O
Broch	O
of	O
West	B-location-island
Burrafirth	I-location-island
hi	O
Iron	O
Age	O
broch	O
a	O
ni	O
a	O
Mainland	B-location-island
,	O
Shetland	B-location-island
(	O
)	O
chhim	O
lamah	O
a	O
awm	O
a	O
ni.	O

Senior	O
a	O
nih	O
laiin	O
.277	O
a	O
vaw	O
chhuak	O
a	O
home	O
run	O
paruk	O
neiin	O
team	O
lead	O
a	O
ni.	O

Coach	O
siamtu	O
leh	O
hralhtu	O
chu	O
Hooper	B-organization-company
&	I-organization-company
Co	I-organization-company
.	I-organization-company
tih	O
chu	O
London	B-location-GPE
ah	O
a	O
ni.	O

Emeric	B-person-politician
,	O
Hungary	B-location-GPE
lal	O
unaunu	O
naupang	O
zawk	O
a	O
ni.	O

A	O
sei	O
zawng	O
chauh	O
ni	O
mah	O
se	O
The	O
Salamander	B-location-mountain
Glacier	I-location-mountain
hi	O
a	O
zau	O
deuh	O
a	O
ni	O
.	O

Video	O
hi	O
Los	B-location-GPE
Angeles	I-location-GPE
-ah	O
The	B-building-other
Echo	I-building-other
,	O
The	B-building-hotel
Standard	I-building-hotel
Hotel	I-building-hotel
leh	O
Downtown	O
kawngpuiah	O
LA	B-location-GPE
-ah	O
te	O
shoot	O
a	O
ni	O
a	O
UK	B-location-GPE
music	O
tastemaker	O
Clash	B-organization-media/newspaper
(	O
magazine	O
)	O
chuan	O
a	O
premiere	O
a	O
ni.	O

Vote	O
thlak	O
hma	O
hian	O
bill	O
te	O
hi	O
Diet	B-organization-government/governmentagency
ah	O
then	O
hran	O
tura	O
ngenna	O
a	O
awm	O
a.	O

